lospec.com 2019-11-01

# Lospec Privacy Policy

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for lospec.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Personal Information We Collect

### Device Information

When you visit Lospec.com, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

This information is collected by Google Analytics and conglomerated through use of an anonymous identifier which is stored on your computer as a cookie. This information is used to gain a general understand of how the site is being used so it can be optimized and improved.

Select actions are also recorded by our server but are not associated with any device information.

You may not opt out of collection of device information and usage data. We do not alter our data collection practices even if you have a "Do Not Track" option enabled in your browser or have installed analytics blocking or ad blocking software that typically blocks google analytics. If you do not wish to be tracked between pages, you can disable cookies in your web browser.

### Order Information

When you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”. 

Personally identifying information is stored by our order processing partner "Shopify" and our fulfillment partner "Printful", but is not saved to Lospec's server. This information is used to fulfill orders, communicate with you about your order and screen orders for potential risk or fraud. If you select the option "Keep me up to date on news and exclusive offers" your email address will also be shared with MailChimp.

Order information such as the amount paid (for products, tax and shipping) and product quantity/variations ordered will be stored by Lospec.

### Contact Information

When you sign up for our newsletter we collect your email address which is stored by MailChimp and used to send future newsletters. You can unsubscribe any time by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of the email.

### How is your personal information used?

Information collected by Lospec and it's 3rd parties is used to fulfill purchases and

Your personal information is not sold or given to additional 3rd parties by Lospec, unless it is required in order to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

## Data Retention

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. Device information cannot be removed.

## Changes to this policy

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. If you wish to receive a notice when these changes take place, you may sign up for our newsletter.

## Contact Us

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by sending an e‑mail to contact at lospec.com or submitting a request through our contact page.

## 3rd Party Privacy Policies

What did you think of this page?
